# **Andy Hayes**

# **Software Engineer**

## **Andy Hayes**

3014 California St. NE Minneapolis, MN 55418

773.391.9185 andrew.c.hayes1@gmail.com https://andyhayes.dev

## **Summary of Qualifications**

High performance computer science graduate from Macalester College. Substantial experience in the service sector gave me strong presentational and communication skills with the ability to lead a group to a common goal. I have experience developing with JavaScript (NodeJS/TS, React), Python, Java, R, SQL, Docker, Kubernetes, GRPC.

## **Experience**

## **Anno.Ai** / Software Engineer

May 2019 - PRESENT, Vienna, VA

Integrated different technologies to automate ML pipelines.

Developed kubernetes orchestrated microservice architecture.

Designed and implemented product features from concept to production.

Contributed/published publicly available Node packages.

Built technologies that work in standalone environments (disconnected from the internet).

Worked with a small team and had impacts on all facets of the application (front/back end, server maintenance/development operations).

#### **Tournament Time /** Founder, Software Developer

Nov. 2018 - May 2019, St. Paul, MN

Started a mobile game development company

Assembled a team and leveraged NodeJS and React Native to develop a beta version of our first project.

Distributed MVP to external users and iterated on early user feedback

#### Education

#### Macalester College / Computer Science, Applied Math

August 2015 - May 2019, St. Paul, MN

Member of baseball team, MacStartups fellow, TA for multiple semesters.

Relevant Coursework: Statistical Modeling, Multivariable Calculus III, Object Oriented Programming, Algorithm Design and Analysis, Software Design and Development, Differential Equations, Computer Systems Organization, Theory of Computation, Probability, Collective Intelligence, Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Database Management Systems